<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Menus on Global Business Services</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/menu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Menus on Global Business Services</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 17:18:40 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/menu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Company</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/company/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 20:42:52 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/company/</guid>
      <description>Infomation about the company</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 20:43:13 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/projects/</guid>
      <description>Our projects</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 20:43:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/services/</guid>
      <description>GBS provides the specialist capability to support clients in the following areas:&#xA;Project management and supervision consulting Project appraisal and evaluation Environmental and social impact assessment and planning Regulatory and institutional framework improvement Design and technical review Procurement support Sector restructuring and commercialisation Economic regulation and quality assurance Investment, operation &amp;amp; market analysis Change management, accounting and financial management Mis and gis Human development and capacity building Project management and supervision consulting GBS is experienced in project management support, including assisting with tendering, evaluation, and contract award to the successful Bidder, issuing the necessary progress reports, and improving the Client&amp;rsquo;s project management capacity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locations</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/locations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 20:43:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/locations/</guid>
      <description>Our locations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 20:44:03 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Since 2002, GBS has been providing professional consulting services in various economic and social fields, including water supply and sanitation, solid waste management, urban infrastructure, agriculture and natural resources management, health management, and other sectors.&#xA;GBS provides high-quality services throughout the project management cycle, from project identification and development to implementation, monitoring, and evaluation. GBS strives to deliver innovative, inclusive, and sustainable solutions for its customers. GBS establishes long-term and successful client partnerships based on trust, respect, professionalism, and goal commitment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 20:44:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>Our contact information</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 17:18:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/</guid>
      <description>Global Business Services Blog</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
